Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Public TV
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 12, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0923 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0923)
    Duration: 2 minutes
    Bill Gunn
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 13, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0924 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0924)
    Clayton Riely and Bill Gunn
    Duration: 98 minutes
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 14, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0925 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0925)
    Scope and Contents
    Discussion: Black Distribution, tape inaudible
    Duration: 79 minutes. Preservation Note: Significant background noise
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 15, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0926 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0926)
    Discussion: tape inaudible
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 16, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0927 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0927)
    Duration: 20 minutes
    Closing remarks
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel A, July 11, 1975; July 12, 1975; ID: 326.0928 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0928)
    Cliff Crawford - "The D & R", James Chen - introducing "The Red Flag Canal", M. Rubbo - "Bates Car: Sweet as a Nut", Mirra Bank - "Yudie"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel B, July 13, 1975; ID: 326.0929 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0929)
    J. Chen introduction and discussion of "Sandstone Gulch"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel C, July 13, 1975; ID: 326.0930 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0930)
    G. Stoney: NYU Student Films, Colin Young: Observational Cinema, A. Lomax: "Dance and Human History"
    Duration: 101 minutes. Preservation note: distortion in first 3 minutes
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel D, July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0931 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0931)
    Duration: 101 minutes
    A. Lomax: Choreometric Study Films, C. Young: Observational Film - "Juvenile Liason Scheme"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel E, July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0932 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0932)
    Duration: 8 minutes
    cont. C. Young: Observational Film - "Juvenile Liason Scheme"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 1, July 10, 1975; July 11, 1975; ID: 326.0933 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0933)
    M. Rubbo - "Waiting for Fidel", Pacific Street Film Collective - "Frame-Up"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 2, July 11, 1975; ID: 326.0934 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0934)
    cont. Pacific Street Film Collective - "Frame-Up", James Chen - "The Red Flag Canal", Yuan-Tsung Chen
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 3, July 11, 1975; July 12; 1975; ID: 326.0935 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0935)
    Susumo Hani - "TVTV Nippon", B. Van Dyke - "Working Mothers"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 4, July 12, 1975; ID: 326.0936 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0936)
    Duration: 76 minutes
    cont. B. Van Dyke - "Working Mothers", C. Weill and A. Slesin - "The Other Hald of the Sky"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 5, July 12, 1975; July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0937 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0937)
    D. Brittain - "Bethune" and "Dreamland", S. Hani - "Children Who Draw"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 6, July 14, 1975; July 15, 1975; ID: 326.0938 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0938)
    S. Hani - "Mio", C. Young - "Mau Mau"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 7, July 15, 1975; ID: 326.0939 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0939)
    Duration: 99 minutes
    D. Leiterman - "One More River", Joyce Campbell - "Companero" and "Dreams & Nightmares"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 8, July 15, 1975; July 16, 1975; ID: 326.0940 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0940)
    cont. Joyce Campbell - "Companero" and "Dreams & Nightmares", W. Van Dyke - Final Discussion
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 9, July 16, 1975; ID: 326.0941 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0941)
    Duration: 75 minutes
    cont. W. Van Dyke - Final Discussion
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 1, May 23, 1976; May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0942 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0942)
    B. Van Dyke, Bill Sloan, D. A. Pennebaker - Opening Remarks D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction of films Bill Miles and Dick Adams - Discussion of "Men of Bronze"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 2, May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0943 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0943)
    Duration: 97 minutes; Preservation note: Speed problems in source for a couple of seconds during the beginning of tape
    L. Kammerling and Sarah Elder - discussion "Space: A Visual Experience" and "On the Spring Ice"
  - Public Television Seminar 1976 Reel 3, May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0944 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0944)
    cont. L. Kammerling and Sarah Elder - discussion "Space: A Visual Experience" and "On the Spring Ice".
    Mary Lampson - discussion of "Lovejoy's Nuclear War" and "Underground"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 4, May 24, 1976; May 25, 1976; ID: 326.0945 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0945)
    Duration: 79 minutes
    cont. Mary Lampson - discussion of "Lovejoy's Nuclear War" and "Underground"
    B. Kopple discussion of labor films: "Blow for Blow," "McKaysville," and "Coal Miners"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 5, May 25, 1976; ID: 326.0946 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0946)
    Discussion of animated films - Eli Noyes, Robert Breer, George Griffin, John Canemaker, Hart Perry
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 6, May 25, 1976; May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0947 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0947)
    Mirra Bank - Discussion of "Pass Me that Club Please", B. Van Dyke - Introduction of "Dagguerotypes", K. Griffith - Introduction of "Edmund Kean",
    D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction of Performance Films, Doris Chase - "Dance 11", Discussion of "Sound of One"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 7, May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0948 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0948)
    Duration: 94 minutes
    D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction to "Monterey Pop" sequence, Susan Woll, Victoria Hochberg, Amy Greenfield, Ed Ernshwiller - Discussion of Performance films, P. Montgomery - Introduction of "Grassroots", J. Schott and J. Vaughn - Introduction of "Commercial Television: Let's Make a Deal"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 8, May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0949 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0949)
    Duration: 89 minutes
    John Schott and Jeff Vaughn - discussion of "Commercial Television Let's Make a Deal", D. A. Pennebaker - discussion of "Grassroots", Warrington Hudlin - introduction and discussion of "Black at Yale", Introduction and discussion of "Potlatch", Introduction - Eva Brown home movies
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 9, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0950 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0950)
    Introduction to science films - Pennebaker, Introduction and discussion of "Crossroads", Introduction and discussion of "Curve Filling Space" with Bill Hansard
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 10, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0951 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0951)
    Discussion "Organism" with Hilary Harris, Discussion "The Clinton Special" with M. Ondaatje, Discussion "Circle in the Fire" with V. Nunez
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 11, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0952 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0952)
    Introduction and discussion of "Family Focus" by Ed and Carol Emshwiller, Discussion of "Tea Party by Susan Woll
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 12, May 27, 1976; May 28, 1976; ID: 326.0953 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0953)
    Introduction and discussion of "Suddenly an Eagle" and "The Pursuit of Happiness" with K. Griffith, Discussion of "Dirty Books," "Menstruation," and Liz Suados work in progress with Linda Feferman, Closing session
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 13, May 28, 1976; ID: 326.0954 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0954)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 1, May 29, 1977; ID: 326.0955 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0955)
    Opening remarks by Bill Sloan and Jay Ruby, Chip Blumberg Ant Farm videotapes (continued Reel 2)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 2, May 29, 1977; May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0956 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0956)
    Continuation Chip Blumberg, Walter Parkes - "California Reich"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 3, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0957 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0957)
    Discussion Japanese relocation camps films, Marianne Lamour "Golden Triangle" (continued on Reel 4)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 4, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0958 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0958)
    Continuation M. Lamour, Alfonso Beato "Puerto Rico - Paradise Invaded"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 5, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0959 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0959)
    Barbara Margolis "On the Line"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 6, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0960 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0960)
    Paul O'Dell "Oklahoma Posse", Jim Klein, Miles Mogulescu, Julia Reichart - "Union Maids" (continued Reel 7)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 7, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0961 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0961)
    Continuation "Union Maids", Grant Munro on films by Caroline Leaf, Alfred Guzzetti "Family Portrait Sittings" (continued on Reel 8)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 8, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0962 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0962)
    Alfred Guzzetti "Family Portrait Sittings" (continued from Reel 7)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 9, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0963 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0963)
    Julie Gustafson "The Politics of Intamicy", Alan and Susan Raymond "Police Tapes"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 10, June 1, 1977; ID: 326.0964 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0964)
    Discussion of "My Childhood", John Reilly and Julie Gustafson "Giving Birth"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 11, June 1, 1977; ID: 326.0965 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0965)
    Steina and Woody Vasulka on their video work, Elaine Baly and Bill Stephens "Uganda Tapes" (continued on Reel 12)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 12, June 1, 1977; June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0966 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0966)
    Duration: 70 minutes
    Continuation of Stephens and Baly on Uganda, Perry Miller Adato "Georgia O'Keeffe", Jay Ruby "The History Book" and "The Incredible Bread Machine"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 13, June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0967 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0967)
    Thom Anderson "Eadweard Muybridge - Zoopraxographer", Anita Thatcher 'Homage to Magritte", General discussion "Brain Surgery" and "Brain...Dynamite..."
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 14, June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0968 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0968)
    Continuation of Reel 13, David Halpern and Jim Guttman "Hollywood on Trial"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 15, June 3, 1977; ID: 326.0969 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0969)
    Linda Feferman "The Girl with the Incredible Feeling", Summary Erik Barnouw, Final discussion (continued on Reel 16)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 16, June 3, 1977; ID: 326.0970 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0970)
    Final discussion (continued from Reel 15)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 1, May 28, 1978; ID: 326.0971 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0971)
    Opening remarks by Jay Ruby and Jack Willis Discussion on "Aguirre"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 2, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0972 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0972)
    Discussion, Dick Rogers on "Elephants" Discussion, "Banks and the Poor"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 3, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0973 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0973)
    Discussion with Judy Irola on "Prarie Fire" and Saul Landau on "The Case Officer" Discussion with Dick Moore on "Lose Just the Same"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 4, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0974 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0974)
    Discussion with Geri Ashur on "Stella and Me" Discussion with Saul Landau on "Que Hacer"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 5, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0975 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0975)
    Discussion Tom Palazzolo on "Hot and Nasty" and Judy Irola on "Self-Health"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 6, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0976 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0976)
    Discussion with Robert Van Lierop on "O Povo Organizado" Discussion with Anne Bohlen on "Babies and Banners"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 7, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0977 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0977)
    Informal discussion on PBS decision making process Discussion with R. Kramer on "Class Struggle in Portugal"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 8, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0978 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0978)
    Jill Godmilow discussing "Popovich Brothers"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 9, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0979 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0979)
    Discussion with Rafael Corkidi on "Pafnucio Santo" Discussion with Pacific St. Film Collective on "Red Squad" (continued on Reel 10)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 10, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0980 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0980)
    Continuation of discussion with Pacific Street Film Collective Discussion with Phil Parmet on "LeRoy the Magician" and Roy Campanella on "Pass/Fail"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 11, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0981 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0981)
    Discussion with Patricio Guzman, Pedro Chaskel, and Rodolfo Broullon on "The Battle of Chile" (continued on Reel 12) (beginning of Guzman's explanation of his methodology is lost due to technical problem)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 12, May 31, 1978; June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0982 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0982)
    Continuation of Reel 11 - Discussion of "The Battle of Chile" (comments by P. Guzman on methodology) Discussion with Kit Laybourne and Mickey Lemle on "Mediaprobe"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 13, June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0983 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0983)
    Discussion with Bill Yahraus on "Home Boys" Discussion with D. Keller and C. Light on "Last Resort"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 14, June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0984 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0984)
    Discussion with Joel Freedman on "Broken Treaty..." Discussion on "We're Not the Jet Set"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 15, June 1, 1978; June 2, 1978; ID: 326.0985 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0985)
    Discussion on "We're Not the Jet Set" (continued from Reel 14) Discussion with Dezso Magyar on "Punitive Expedition" Final discussion with summary of the week by Eric Barnouw (continued on Reel 16)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 16, June 2, 1978; ID: 326.0986 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0986)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 1, May 28, 1979; ID: 326.0987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0987)
    Opening discussion with Mitch Block - Speeding and Alain [Tanners] films
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 2, May 28, 1979; ID: 326.0988 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0988)
    Opening discussion with Mitch Block (continued from Reel 1)
    Jonathan Lewis - Before Hindsight
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 2A, [May 28, 1979]; ID: 326.0989 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0989)
    Discussion of Northern Ireland with Jon Lewis (continued from Reel 2)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 3, May 28, 1979; May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0990)
    Jonathan Lewis discussion (continued from Reel 2 and Reel 2A)
    Faith Hubley - The Carousel of Life
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 4, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0991 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0991)
    Sonntag
    Neils - Peter Rudolph
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 5, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0992 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0992)
    Niels Peter - Sonntag (continued from Reel 4), Anita Thatcher, Dick Adams
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 6, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0993 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0993)
    Eckhardt Stein - Night Hawks
    Bob Lowler, Chris Banford, Jim Morton - Reflections
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 7, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0994 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0994)
    Bob Lowler, Chris Bamford, Jim Morton - Reflections
    Jan Krawitz, Thomas Ott, Ross Lowell
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 8, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0995 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0995)
    Ira Woll, Roland Joffe
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 9, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0996 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0996)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 10, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0997 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0997)
    Barry Braverman, James Kennedy - [Doctoring]
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 11, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.0998 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0998)
    George Griffin
    Joel Gold, Maxi Cohen
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 12, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.0999 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.0999)
    Joel Gold, Maxi Cohen,
    Richard Harkness - inside San Quentin
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 13, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.1000 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1000)
    Richard Harkness (continued from Reel 12)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 14, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.1001 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1001)
    Yolando MacShane discussion
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 15, ID: 326.1002 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1002)
    Yolanda MacShane - Public TV and Independents discussion
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 16, May 31, 1979; June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1003 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1003)
    Yolanda MacShane - discussion of Public TV and Independents (continued from Reel 15)
    Jim Day - discussion of Nixon Film
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 17, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1004 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1004)
    Jim Day - discussion of Nixon Film (continued from Reel 16)
    Wrap up
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 18, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1005 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1005)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 19, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1006 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 326.1006)
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 1, June 1, 1980; ID: 326.1007 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1007)
    Introduction by Jay Ruby
    Programmers intro: Jaime Barrios, Alfred Guzzetti, Ralph Maradiaga, George Horsecapture, David Lacy
    Barrio's intro plus house intro
    Film: El Super
    Discussion Leon Ichasco, Manuel Arce also Jaime Barrio
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 2, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1008 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1008)
    Films: Los Venditos- Luis Ruis
    Campaign Against Racism
    Stuart Hall
    Discussion: Luis Ruis, Mike Fentiman also Davis Lacy, Ralph Maradiaga
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 3, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1009 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1009)
    "56 1/2 Howard St" plus "Mission Hill and the Miracle of Boston"- R. Broadman discussion with Richard Broadman and Alfred Guzzetti
    Films: Listen Curacas
    The Price we Paid Raymond Young
    discussion: Raymond Young, George Horsecapture, Jaime Barrio
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 4, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1010 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1010)
    Continues from Tape 3
    Raymond Young's The Price we Paid
    Films Italiamerican Scorcese, Simplimente Jenny Helena Ladd, discussion: Helena Ladd, Jaime Barrio, Alfred Guzzetti
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 5, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1011 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1011)
    Continues from Tape 4
    Discussion by Helena Ladd, Simplimente Jenny
    Transmagnification Dambamuality, Ronald Gray, Killer of Sheep, Charles Burnett
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 6, June 2-3, 1980; ID: 326.1012 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1012)
    Continues from Tape 5: Killer of Sheep, Charles Burnett
    Images- Great Movie Massacre, We Remember by Raymond Yakeleya, George Horse Catcher (June 3rd)
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 7, June 3, 1980; ID: 326.1013 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1013)
    "Agueda Martinez" Moctezuma Esparza, discussion also with Ralph Maradiaga
    We are Workers, Antonnio Parra
    Discussion with Antonnio Parra and Ralph Maradiaga, Raquel Ortiz
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 8, June 3, 1980; ID: 326.1014 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1014)
    Years of Longing, Diego Echeria. Discussion with Jaime Barrio and Diego Echeria
    Spikes to Spindles, Chris Choy. Discussion with Alfred Guzzetti
    Also: The Cruz Brothers and Mrs. Malloy by Kathleen Collins
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 9, June 3, 1980; ID: 326.1015 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1015)
    Continues from Tape 8
    The Cruz Brothers and Mrs. Malloy, K. Collins
    Also: Film: After the Earthquake by Lourdes Portillo with Ralph Maradiaga
    Also: Film: Billy in the Lowlands, discussion with Jan Egleson, David Luoy, Alfred Guzzetti
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 10, June 3-4, 1980; ID: 326.1016 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1016)
    Continues from Tape 9 for ten minutes, then- June 4- VTR: "I don't matter, I don't care" Michael Marton
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 11, June 4, 1980; ID: 326.1017 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1017)
    Continues from Tape 10
    Awakening by Larry Little Bird
    China: Land of My Father, Felicia Lowe
    Tule Indians by Eden Velez discussion also with Jaime Barrio
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 12, June 4, 1980; ID: 326.1018 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1018)
    VTR Ancestors of those Unborn by George Burdeau, Discussion with George Horsecapture, Also SALSA by Jeremy Marre, Discussion with David Lacy
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 13, June 4, 1980; ID: 326.1019 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1019, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.1019_pt.1, Cd 326.1019_pt.2)
    Film Clarence and The Angel by Bob Gardner discussion with Jaime Barrio and David Lacy
    Continues with The Laughing Alligator by Juan Downey, Discussion with Jaime Barrio, Continued on Tape 14
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 14, June 5, 1980; ID: 326.1020 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1020)
    Ten Minutes on Juan Downey from Tape 13 (June 4th)
    Continues: Wyld Ryce and Heart of the Earth, Survival School, by Chris Spotted Eagles, discussion with George Horsecapture, Also: Unwanted by Luis Ruiz, Discussion with Ralph Maradiaga
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 15, June 5, 1980; ID: 326.1021 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1021)
    Continued from Tape 14: Film Unwanted by Luis Ruiz
    VTR Real Indians by Paul Lucas and Statements by all Native Americans present.
    Note: Larry Little Birds song erased by request.
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 16, June 5, 1980; ID: 326.1022 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1022)
    Film Loisaida by Marci Reaven and Beni Matias
    Discussion with Ralph Maradiaga
    Note: No Head Slate, Mistake of Short Mis-Recorded Section
    Also: To be young, gifted, and black by Gloria Mike Schultz
    Discussion with Gloria and David Lacy
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 17, June 6, 1980; ID: 326.1023 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1023)
    Introduction: Jay Ruby, Barbara Van Dyke, Erik Barnouw, EVERYONE
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 18, June 6, 1980; ID: 326.1024 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1024)
    Continued from Tape 17